

## **PROFILE**

Solution-driven Web Developer who is adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment.

Finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction.

Built products for desktop and web app users over 8+ years, meeting the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, and speed.

Possess strong attention to detail, well-developed time management skills, and the ability to complete all projects within schedule and in a timely manner.

# **CONTACT**

**EMAIL** 

arian.mobarghei@gmail.com

PHONE:

+98 912 517 6301

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/arian-mobarghei-10697313b

GITHUB:

github.com/arian22

# **PORTFOLIO**

https://arian22.github.io/portfolio/

# ARIAN MOBARGHEI

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Full Stack Developer**

**Vesta Wealth Partners** (Oct 2020 – Present)

Built and developed two web portals for generating reports using Django template and D3. Secure document delivery to the client using private S3 bucket on AWS.

Built and develop the new client portal for three branches to let new customers fill out their forms.

redbarnportal.ca clients.pliriswealth.com westawealth.partners

Technology: Python & Django & DRF & PostgreSQL & Docker & AWS & S3 Bucket & D3 & Bitbucket & Git

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Self-employed (Jan 2020 - Oct 2020)

Developed a web application, "<u>aratsystem.ir</u>" for restaurants that allow customers to scan the menu and order their food.

Developed a web application for individual gold-retailer to trade gold from their wholesale. (Over 1,000+ deals per day)

Technology: Python & Django & DRF & PostgreSQL & Redis & Vue.js

#### Web Developer

Zarrin, Tehran, Iran (Sep 2014 – Jan 2020)

Developed an e-commerce web app, customer web portal.

Launch a website for a local charity "taj-gol.ir"

Creating and running a service for selling goods in the local network.

Technology: PHP & MySQL & HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery & D3 Graph & Bootstrap & OOP & Git

## **EDUCATION**

## **Azad University**

June 2014

**Bachelor of Computer Engineering** 

# **CHARACTERISTICS**

- Creativity & Hard worker
- Excellent listener
- Problem-Solving Abilities